&gt；&gt；Kyle：我们已经讨论过函数作用域，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: We've talked about function scoping,
现在让我们将注意力转移到阻止作用域。
let's shift our attention now to block scoping.
像听起来那样阻止范围，
Block scoping like it sounds,
它的作用域是用块(也称为花括号)而不是函数完成的。
it's scoping that's done with blocks aka curly braces instead of with functions.
同样的原则也适用。
Same principle is gonna apply.
我们想把一些东西放在一个块里而不是封闭的里面
We wanna put something inside of a block instead of inside of the enclosing
作用域，因为我们想要隐藏它，以便它有更少的名称冲突的机会。
scope because we wanna hide it, so that it has fewer chances of name collision.
我们想保护细节，保护未来的重构，
We wanna protect a detail, protect future refactoring,
所有的原则都适用。
all the same principle applies.
只是我们现在使用的机制是块范围声明，而不是
It's just the mechanism we use is now a block scope declaration instead of
例如，一种生活。
an IIFE, for example.
所以，与其写生命，不如用一块木块来写。
So Instead of writing an IIFE, let's write it with a block.
你可以从心理上比较这个例子和
And you can compare mentally the difference between that example with
一种生活方式，或者只是使用花括号块并使用let语句，如
an IIFE or just using a curly braced block and using a let statement like
块状范围装饰，&gt；&gt；Kyle：它要轻得多
a block scope decoration, &gt;&gt; Kyle: It's a lot lighter
重量不是吗？
weight isn't it?.
它也有较少的副作用，因为它没有重新定义任何东西
It also has less side effects in the sense it doesn't redefined anything about
返回或中断或任何其他内容，因此块更容易一些，
returns or breaks or any of that other stuff, so blocks are a bit easier and
将较轻的重量放在适当的地方。
lighter weight to put into places.
它们不是表情，所以
They're not expressions, so
不能在可以使用表达式的地方使用它们。
you can't use them in places where you can use expressions.
但如果你把它们放在一个声明的地方，那是完全没问题的。
But if you have them in a place that's a statement, it's totally okay.
有时更可取的是只做这种重量较轻的形式，
And sometimes often a lot more preferable to just do this lighter weight form,
将一对卷曲的大括号包在某物上，然后
wrap a curly brace pair around something and
在它里面做一个块作用域声明。
make a block scope declaration inside of it.
现在你不能只在这里做var，因为历史上var一直是
Now you can't just do a var here because historically vars have been
将自己附加到外部函数作用域或全局作用域。
attaching themselves to the outer function scope or global scope.
所以这里的var会将自己附加到外部范围而不是卷曲的范围
So a var here would have attached itself to the outer scope rather than the curly
支架对。
brace pair.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：不是打破旧的向后或旧的先前代码，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Instead of breaking old backward or old previous code,
他们决定增加新的申报单。
they decided to add new declaration forms.
所以这就是我们得到let和const的地方。
So it's where we get the let and the const from.
let和const，以便您可以在块内进行声明，并
Let and const are so that you can make a declaration inside of a block and
它把那个块变成了一个示波器。
it turns that block into a scope.
块不是作用域，除非它们内部有let或const，并且
Blocks are not scopes until they have a let or const inside of them and
那么这种隐含地使它们成为一个作用域。
then that sort of implicitly makes them a scope.
那是一个关键的地方，人们可以在那里得到，
That's a key place where people sort of get,
他们认为所有的花括号都是作用域，它们并不都是作用域。
they think that all curly braces are scopes, and they're not all scopes.
如果里面有let或const，它们只是一个作用域。
They're only a scope if there's a let or a const inside of it.
好的，所以这是一个轻量级的方式来做这个特别的例子。
Okay, so this was a lightweight way of doing this particular example.
但是块作用域在更大的范围内适合在哪里呢？
But where does block scoping fit in the larger scope of things?
我要声明你应该用块作用域做什么
I'm gonna make the claim that what you should be doing with block scoping
使用类似let关键字的内容来加强
is using something like the let keyword to reinforce
一些你本来就很自然地想要传达给你的读者的东西。
something that you would have already naturally wanted to signal to your reader.
这里有一个例子。
Here's an example.
如果您正在编写需要临时语句的if语句的代码
If you were writing code where you had an if statement that needed a temporary
变量来做一些事情，在这种情况下交换两个值。
variable to do something, in this case to swap two values.
你叫它tmp是为了给读者发信号，
And you called it tmp to signal to the reader,
这只是一个临时的占位符，我并不是真的用得太多。
it's just a temporary placeholder, I'm not really using it for much.
当然，我把var tmp放在if里面，因为我想说
And definitely, I put the var tmp inside of the if because I'm trying to say to
读者，你不需要访问这个或在其他任何地方使用这个。
the reader, you don't need to access this or use this anywhere else.
我们知道var的行为方式是它将自己附着在
We know that the way var behaves is that it'll attach itself to
蓝色的望远镜，对吧？
the blue scope, right?
它将是一个蓝色的大理石附在整个功能上，如果。
It'll be a blue marble attached to the whole function if.
但我们发出的是某种风格上的信号，
But we're signaling something stylistically,
在语义上对读者来说，也就是说，这个变量属于if语句。
semantically to the reader which is to say this variable belongs to the if statement.
如果你做这样的事情，你们中的一些人可能把你的vars放在if里面
If you do stuff like this, and some of you may have put your vars inside of if
语句或之前的其他类型的块
statements or other sorts of blocks before or
也许您将var语句放在for循环中。
maybe you put your var statements inside of for loops.
这是很常见的事情。
That's a very common thing.
如果你已经这样做了，那么你已经在发出的信号是，
If you've done that, then what you were already signalling was,
无论您是否意识到，嘿读者，这是一个块范围的变量。
whether you realized it or not, hey reader, this is a block scoped variable.
现在我们有了块范围声明，您可以安全地替换这些
And now that we have a block scope declaration, you can safely replace those
现在你正在实施你已经在文体上发出信号的东西。
and now you are enforcing the thing that you were already stylistically signalling.
我认为这是接近这个特征的适当方式，也就是说，
That I think is the appropriate way to approach this feature which is to say,
您应该在已经很明显且设计正确的地方使用它
you should use it in places where it is already obvious and correct design for
你要阻挡范围内的东西。
you to block scope something.
我认为你不应该去寻找更多的机会
I do not think that you should go looking for opportunities to more
通过更多的块作用域使代码复杂化
complexify your code by having more block scoping for
没有特别的原因，只是为了你可以使用这个热门的新的let关键字。
no particular reason, just so you can use this hot new let keyword.
你应该在阻止作用域已经有意义的地方使用它，好吗？
You should use it in places where it already makes sense to block scope, okay?
所以这是我想要在你的第一次轮班
So that's the first shift that I wanna have in your
心智思考就是把它看作是对
mental thinking is to think about that as a replacement for
您已经用语义标记的块作用域。
your already semantically signalled block scope.
顺便说一句，我不是这种劫持望远镜的狂热粉丝，因为我
I'm not a big fan by the way of this hijacking of scopes because I
通常认为if语句只是if语句。
normally think of an if statement as just an if statement.
但现在我必须查看if语句的全部内容才能弄清楚
But now I have to look through the entire contents of an if statement to figure out
如果其中有let关键字，并确定这是否也是一个作用域。
if there's a let keyword in it and figure out if that's also a scope.
如果它是一个示波器，我必须更加小心我移动的东西和
And if it is a scope I have to be more careful about what I move around and
我可以把什么放在哪里。
where I can put what.
所以我不是很喜欢这种隐含的劫机行为，但是
So I'm not a big fan of that whole implicit hijacking thing but
我很喜欢能够执行我们已经发出信号的东西
I am a fan of being able to enforce the thing that we were already signaling
也就是说，我希望这个东西是本地化的。
which is, I want this thing to be local.
那么这整个let是新的var的东西呢？
So what about this whole let is the new var thing?
我相信你以前也听过这句话
I'm sure you've heard this before,
事实上，即使用const替换的是新的let。
as a matter of fact that's been replaced even with const is the new let.
有字面上的T恤衫，和
There were literally T-Shirts made, and
穿着TC39年前的一些成员说，让是新的var。
worn by some members of TC39 years back that said, let is the new var.
这是一个横幅。
This was a banner.
有一个TC39成员的博客帖子说，只要做一个全球搜索，
And there was a blog post by a TC39 member that said, just do a global find and
在您的程序上替换，并用一个let替换所有出现的var。
replace on your program and replace all occurrences with var with a let.
这是一个非常愚蠢的建议。
That is an enormously stupid piece of advice.
请不要那样做。
Please do not do that.
这是个糟糕的主意。
It's a terrible idea.
您不仅几乎肯定会产生bug，而且
Not only are you almost certainly to create bugs, but
更重要的是，您正在误用该功能。
importantly than that, you're misusing that feature.
与你在这门课上从我身上看到的一切一致，
Consistent with everything you've already seen from me in this course,
我要告诉你的是，let不仅仅是一些全面的
I'm gonna tell you that let is not just some across-the-board
var关键字的替换。
replacement of the var keyword.
但它是一个额外的工具，我们应该添加到现有的使用中
But it is an additional tool that we should add on to our existing usage
这意味着仍然有理由使用var关键字。
which means that there are still reasons to use the var keyword.
与我的同龄人相比，这同样具有争议性或不同寻常
And that is similarly controversial or unusual compared to my peers who
会告诉你永远，永远不要再使用var关键字。
would tell you never, ever, ever use the var keyword ever again.
我会一直告诉你var关键字是有目的。
And I'm gonna keep telling you the var keyword has purpose.
这里有一个例子。
Here's an example.
在这段代码中，我们有两个var。
In this code, we have two vars.
我们有一个var，它在for循环中，并且
We have a var that's on a for loop, and
我们有一个var，它基本上在整个函数中使用。
we have a var that's essentially being used across the entire function.